<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><data><meters display="on"><meter id="P1" type="MONEY" initialValue="0" maxValue="25000" minValue="0" valueDiff="5000" prefix="$" suffix="" header=" " footer=" " label="Money" position="Left"></meter></meters><slides><slide id="I1" type="intro" next_screen_id="E1"><slidetext><![CDATA[The Civil War in Syria, which began in 2011, is the worst humanitarian crisis of the 21st century. It has forced millions of Syrians to become refugees, seeking asylum in foreign countries. ]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[How would you fare as a refugee?]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="E1" type="exposition" next_screen_id="E2" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="5"><slidetext><![CDATA[You live in a small town in Syria that is under attack. You, your spouse, and your three children are no longer safe.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="E2" type="exposition" next_screen_id="E3" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="5"><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family, who are part of the Syrian Kurdish minority, have heard that Germany may be welcoming refugees.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="E3" type="exposition" next_screen_id="E4" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="5"><slidetext><![CDATA[You have no savings but could sell your home and belongings to fund the journey with your family of five.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="E4" type="exposition" next_screen_id="D1" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="4"><slidetext><![CDATA[What do you do?]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1" type="decision" layout="type1"><qtext><![CDATA[Do you sell your home and what you can of your belongings for a fraction of their value in order to leave Syria and pursue safety in Germany?]]></qtext><options><option id="1" next_screen_id="D1_O1_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Sell everything and abandon what you can’t sell]]></main_text><sub_text><![CDATA[The cost of getting to Germany can vary wildly, and there is no guarantee the price you get for your house and belongings will be enough.]]></sub_text></option><option id="2" next_screen_id="D1_O2_T"><main_text><![CDATA[Stay in Syria]]></main_text><sub_text><![CDATA[Many of your neighbors are leaving their homes and fleeing to a nearby city that so far has seemed relatively safe.]]></sub_text></option></options></slide><slide id="D1_O1_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_C1" param1="+25000" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You sell your home and belongings for $25,000]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[This will provide the funds you need to begin your journey to Germany, where you hope to gain refugee status for your family and qualify for assistance.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_C1" type="connection" next_screen_id="D1_O1_E1"><slidetext><![CDATA[According to the United Nations, there are over 65 million refugees and internally displaced people around the world. In 2016, 55% of refugees worldwide came from Syria, Afghanistan, and South Sudan. ]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_E1" type="exposition" next_screen_id="D1_O1_EV1" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="5"><slidetext><![CDATA[You now have $25,000 from the sale of your home but must leave most of your belongings behind unsold.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_EV1" type="event" next_screen_id="D1_O1_E2" param1="-500" param2=" "><slidetext><![CDATA[You find someone who charges you $500 to get you and your family across the border into neighboring Lebanon.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_E2" type="exposition" next_screen_id="D1_O1_E3" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="5"><slidetext><![CDATA[Lebanon is overcrowded with refugees and has high poverty and unemployment. Anti-refugee sentiment is on the rise.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_E3" type="exposition" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="4"><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family agree to continue your journey toward Germany.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2" type="decision" layout="type1"><qtext><![CDATA[To get to Europe, you must go through Turkey or Egypt. Either way, you will probably have to be smuggled. Which route do you take?]]></qtext><options><option id="1" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Through Turkey]]></main_text><sub_text><![CDATA[You can get to Europe from Turkey by land. The flight from Beirut to Istanbul will cost $2,500 for you and your family. Travel visas are not required.]]></sub_text></option><option id="2" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Through Egypt]]></main_text><sub_text><![CDATA[The journey to Europe from Egypt is by sea. Flights from Beirut to Cairo will cost $2,000 for you and your family, plus $400 total for travel visas.]]></sub_text></option></options></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_C1" param1="-2500" param2=" "><slidetext><![CDATA[You choose to go through Turkey]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family arrive in Istanbul, where you manage to find a small apartment.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_C1" type="connection" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_EV1"><slidetext><![CDATA[In 2016, Turkey accepted 2.9 million Syrian refugees, making it the largest host-community of displaced Syrians in the world. Anti-refugee feeling among the Turkish people is high.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_EV1" type="event" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_E1" param1="-1250" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[After two weeks in Istanbul, you have spent $1,250 of your money on food and shelter. You have also received harassment and threats when out in public.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_E1" type="exposition" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="5"><slidetext><![CDATA[You meet a smuggler, Khalid. He doesn’t seem entirely trustworthy, but he says he can get you and your family to Europe.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3" type="decision" layout="type3"><qtext><![CDATA[What decision do you and your family make?]]></qtext><options><option id="1" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O1_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[You stay in Istanbul.]]></main_text></option><option id="2" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[You pay Khalid $3,000 per person to travel by sea to Greece. Traveling by sea is physically riskier&#8212;boats often capsize&#8212;but you are less likely to get caught.]]></main_text></option><option id="3" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[You pay Khalid $4,000 per person to travel by land to Greece. Traveling by land is physically safer, but you are more likely to get caught.]]></main_text></option></options></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O1_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O1_EV1" param1="-2500" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You stay in Istanbul]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[Unfortunately, you and your family are unable to find jobs and begin to burn through your small savings. You go to work in the informal economy as street vendors. ]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O1_EV1" type="event" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O1_T" param1="-18250" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[The government decides to crack down on the Kurdish community. All your money and belongings are confiscated.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O1_T" type="termination" next_screen_id="I1"><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your entire family are sent to live indefinitely in a refugee camp for Syrians, where conditions are very poor. You see no hope of conditions improving in Syria enough for you to return, and there is now no chance of making it to Germany.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4" param1="-15000" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You travel by sea to Greece]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family have paid Khalid $15,000 to lead you by sea to Greece. After meeting Khalid by cover of night at the meeting point to board the boat, you discover that you and your family will be separated&#8212;men and boys on one boat, women and girls on the other.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4" type="decision" layout="type2"><qtext><![CDATA[Do you split up and continue the journey by sea or stay in Istanbul?]]></qtext><options><option id="1" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O1_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Split up]]></main_text></option><option id="2" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O2_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Stay]]></main_text></option></options></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O1_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O1_C1" param1="" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family split up]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[Both boats are in poor condition. The next morning, after a terrifying night, your boat arrives on the shores of Lesvos, a Greek island. The other boat, which your spouse and two children boarded, never appears. After waiting all day, word spreads through the smugglers’ network that the other boat capsized and everyone is feared to have drowned.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O1_C1" type="connection" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O1_T"><slidetext><![CDATA[Children below 18 years of age constituted about half of the refugee population in 2016.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O1_T" type="termination" next_screen_id="I1"><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your remaining child turn yourselves in to Greek authorities. You are processed and indefinitely held in a refugee detention center, where conditions are squalid. ]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O2_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O2_EV1" param1="-2500" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You decide to stay in Istanbul]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[Khalid refuses to return your money when you decline to split up for the sea journey. You and your family return to Istanbul with fewer resources. You are unable to find jobs and begin to burn through what’s left of your savings. You go to work in the informal economy as street vendors. ]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O2_EV1" type="event" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O2_T" param1="-3250" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[The government decides to crack down on the Kurdish community. All your money and belongings are confiscated.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O2_D4_O2_T" type="termination" next_screen_id="I1"><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your entire family are sent to live indefinitely in a refugee camp for Syrians, where conditions are very poor. You see no hope of conditions improving in Syria enough for you to return, and there is now no chance of making it to Germany.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_D4" param1="-20000" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You have paid Khalid $20,000 to go by land to Greece]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[You arrive safely but must decide whether to remain in Greece, where poverty is high, employment opportunities are few, and the country has very few resources to deal with the massive numbers of Syrian refugees.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_D4" type="decision" layout="type1"><qtext><![CDATA[What decision do you and your family make?]]></qtext><options><option id="1" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_D4_O1_T"><main_text><![CDATA[Stay in Greece]]></main_text><sub_text><![CDATA[You will try to make the best of things.]]></sub_text></option><option id="2" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_D4_O2_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Continue on foot to Germany]]></main_text><sub_text><![CDATA[You must go without a guide, as you have very little money left.]]></sub_text></option></options></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_D4_O1_T" type="termination" next_screen_id="I1"><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family decide to remain in Greece. You are processed as refugees by the Greek government and detained indefinitely in a United Nations&#8211;sponsored camp. Living conditions are very poor, and you have little hope of leaving the camp in the foreseeable future.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_D4_O2_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_D4_O2_C1" param1="-250" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You decide to walk to Germany]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family begin the long journey on foot to Germany, following other refugees. Your progress is slow, as blisters, inclement weather, hunger, and sickness impede your journey.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_D4_O2_C1" type="connection" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_D4_O2_T"><slidetext><![CDATA[The United Nations Refugee Agency reports a number of health risks for displaced people, including malnutrition, tuberculosis, vector-borne disease, sexually transmitted infections, and emotional stress.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O1_D3_O3_D4_O2_T" type="termination" next_screen_id="I1"><slidetext><![CDATA[You finally reach the Hungarian border, where a border fence has been erected. You are taken into custody by Hungarian border guards and are indefinitely detained in a refugee camp, where conditions are very poor.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_EV1" param1="-2400" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You decide to go through Egypt]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family have arrived in Egypt. However, conditions in Egypt are as poor as they were in Lebanon, and your visas are valid for only three months.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_EV1" type="event" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_C1" param1="-750" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[After two weeks in Cairo, you have spent $750 of your money on food and substandard shelter. Your visa does not allow you to work, and there are few jobs anyway.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_C1" type="connection" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3"><slidetext><![CDATA[Children below 18 years of age constituted about half of the refugee population in 2016.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3" type="decision" layout="type3"><qtext><![CDATA[You meet a smuggler, Khalid. He doesn’t seem entirely trustworthy, but he says he can get you and your family to Europe. What do you do?]]></qtext><options><option id="1" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O1_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Stay in Cairo and work as street vendors.]]></main_text></option><option id="2" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Travel to Alexandria, Egypt, and then on by sea to Italy, at greater risk of being caught and deported. Cost: $4,000 per family member.]]></main_text></option><option id="3" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Travel to Benghazi in Libya. There are dangerous militia groups along the way, but the eventual journey by sea to Italy will be shorter. Cost: $4,200 per family member.]]></main_text></option></options></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O1_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O1_T" param1="-4000" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You stay in Cairo]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family go to work in the informal economy as street vendors. You spend much more than you earn but have your savings as a cushion. After three months, your visas expire. Afraid of expulsion, you do not try to renew them.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O1_T" type="termination" next_screen_id="I1"><slidetext><![CDATA[Four months later, you are arrested for illegally selling goods on the street. The police detain you indefinitely, and you never see your family again.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_EV1" param1="-10100" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You decide to travel to Alexandria]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[You take a very long bus journey there at the cost of $100. Once there, Khalid puts you up in a squalid one-bedroom apartment and demands $2,000 per family member as a deposit for your onward journey. He tells you not to leave the apartment, as conditions are dangerous.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_EV1" type="event" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_C1" param1="" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[As a result of close confinement in the dirty apartment, all members of your family have contracted norovirus. You experience severe nausea, vomiting, and diarrhea. ]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_C1" type="connection" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_E1"><slidetext><![CDATA[The United Nations Refugee Agency reports a number of health risks for displaced people, including malnutrition, tuberculosis, vector-borne disease, sexually transmitted infections, and emotional stress. ]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_E1" type="exposition" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_E2" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="4"><slidetext><![CDATA[After one terrible week inside the apartment, Khalid returns. He says that everything is arranged.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_E2" type="exposition" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_D4" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="5"><slidetext><![CDATA[You are slowly recovering from the norovirus, but you still feel very weak. Khalid says you must leave now.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_D4" type="decision" layout="type1"><qtext><![CDATA[Do you stay in Alexandria or pay the remaining $10,000 to travel on to Italy?]]></qtext><options><option id="1" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_D4_O1_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Travel on to Italy]]></main_text><sub_text><![CDATA[You pay the remaining $10,000 and report by cover of night to the specified location to board the boat.]]></sub_text></option><option id="2" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_D4_O2_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Stay in Alexandria]]></main_text><sub_text><![CDATA[You feel too weak from your recent illness and decide to stay.]]></sub_text></option></options></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_D4_O1_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_D4_O1_T" param1="-10000" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You decide to travel on to Italy]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family pay the $10,000 and board the boat, which is in very poor condition. A sudden storm has stalled your departure. Travel conditions are now too dangerous to sail and you must shelter in the boat with your family until the storms pass. You are becoming anxious as to whether your family will survive this journey.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_D4_O1_T" type="termination" next_screen_id="I1"><slidetext><![CDATA[The storms pass, and you are finally able to disembark. After two days at sea, during which you are hungry, seasick, and forced to stay below deck, your boat capsizes. Many on board drown before the rest of you are rescued by the Italian coast guard. You and your family are indefinitely held in a refugee detention center, where conditions are squalid.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_D4_O2_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_D4_O2_T" param1="-4000" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You stay in Alexandria]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[Khalid refuses to return your deposit. You and your family go to work in the informal economy as street vendors. You spend much more than you earn, but you have what’s left of your savings as a cushion. After three months, your visas expire. Afraid of expulsion, you do not try to renew them.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O2_D4_O2_T" type="termination" next_screen_id="I1"><slidetext><![CDATA[After four months, you are arrested for illegally selling goods on the street. The police detain you indefinitely, and you never see your family again.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_EV1" param1="-15000" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You decide to go to Benghazi]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family travel with Khalid by car to Libya. It is a very dangerous journey, but you are lucky and are not intercepted by militias. You have paid $3,000 each as a deposit on your journey. On arrival in Libya, Khalid puts you up in a squalid one-bedroom apartment. He tells you not to leave the apartment, as conditions are dangerous.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_EV1" type="event" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_C1" param1="" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[As a result of close confinement in the dirty apartment, all members of your family have contracted norovirus. You experience severe nausea, vomiting, and diarrhea. ]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_C1" type="connection" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_E1"><slidetext><![CDATA[The United Nations Refugee Agency reports a number of health risks for displaced people, including malnutrition, tuberculosis, vector-borne disease, sexually transmitted infections, and emotional stress. ]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_E1" type="exposition" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_E2" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="4"><slidetext><![CDATA[After one terrible week inside the apartment, Khalid returns. He says that everything is arranged. ]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_E2" type="exposition" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_D4" font_variation="smaller" animation_time="5"><slidetext><![CDATA[You are slowly recovering from the norovirus, but you still feel very weak. Khalid says you must leave now.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_D4" type="decision" layout="type1"><qtext><![CDATA[Do you stay in Benghazi or pay the remaining $6,000 to travel on to Italy?]]></qtext><options><option id="1" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_D4_O1_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Travel on to Italy]]></main_text><sub_text><![CDATA[You pay the remaining $6,000 and report by cover of night to the specified location to board the boat.]]></sub_text></option><option id="2" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_D4_O2_R1"><main_text><![CDATA[Stay in Benghazi]]></main_text><sub_text><![CDATA[Feeling too weak from your recent illness, you decide to stay.]]></sub_text></option></options></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_D4_O1_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_D4_O1_T" param1="-6000" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You travel on to Italy]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[You and your family pay the $6,000 and board the boat, which is in very poor condition. After two days at sea, during which you are hungry, seasick, and forced to stay below deck, your boat is intercepted by the Italian coast guard.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_D4_O1_T" type="termination" next_screen_id="I1"><slidetext><![CDATA[You have made it to Europe, but you and your family are indefinitely held in a refugee detention center, where conditions are squalid.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_D4_O2_R1" type="result" next_screen_id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_D4_O2_T" param1="-2000" param2=""><slidetext><![CDATA[You stay in Benghazi]]></slidetext><slidetext><![CDATA[It is too dangerous to stay in Benghazi, but Khalid refuses to return your money or take you back to Cairo. You find another smuggler who will drive you back to Cairo for $2,000.]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O1_D2_O2_D3_O3_D4_O2_T" type="termination" next_screen_id="I1"><slidetext><![CDATA[Desperate, you pay the smuggler and make the journey. However, you are intercepted by an armed militia en route. They rob and execute you and your family. ]]></slidetext></slide><slide id="D1_O2_T" type="termination" next_screen_id="I1"><slidetext><![CDATA[Before you have a chance to leave for the nearby city, bombs from an air raid destroy your home as you sleep. You and your family are killed.]]></slidetext></slide></slides></data>